roadid.com 2016-06-09

# Road ID® - Privacy Policy

Legally, we're required to issue and adhere to a fancy legalistic privacy policy. Our philosophy on privacy, however, is far simpler than all the legal mumbo jumbo that our attorneys so kindly drafted (below). We, the owners of Road ID, place a great value on our own personal privacy and security. We believe that your personal information is just as important as our own. So, we absolutely refuse to share your personal information with any unauthorized business, organization, or individual. We promise.

Edward Wimmer  
Mike Wimmer  
Owners, Road ID 

### OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT TO YOU

Road ID recognizes, respects, and protects the personal privacy rights of all of our customers who provide information to us on our websites, via email or through the Road ID App. We realize that our customers entrust us with non-public personal information ("NPI") and it is our obligation and policy to maintain this information in a confidential manner. We are committed to providing the highest level of security and privacy regarding the maintenance and use of our customer's NPI. 

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF NON-PUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION

All of the NPI we collect about you is provided by you. Internally, we restrict access to your NPI to those employees who need to view the information in order to provide to you valuable Road ID services. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable standards to guard your NPI. 

If you use the Road ID APP, the NPI you provide for the lock screen feature of the Road ID App is neither collected nor stored by Road ID; such information is stored only on your mobile device. As with any mobile device, the information on your lock screen and within the Road ID App may be accessed by anyone in possession of your mobile device. 

If you purchase an Interactive Road ID and use the Emergency Response System, you will decide which NPI to supply in your Emergency Response Profile (ERP). Access to this information is granted to anyone that supplies the unique serial number and pin combination that is engraved on the back of your Interactive Road ID. Accordingly, we urge you to protect the security of your Emergency Response Profile by safeguarding the unique serial number and pin on your Interactive ID(s). Only provide these numbers to persons or entities who have a legitimate need to access your ERP. In an emergency, any First Responder that has access to the back of your Interactive ID can use the serial number and pin to access your ERP. 

### SHARING INFORMATION

Please be assured we will never sell your name, address, email address or other NPI to third parties, nor do we share your NPI with any third parties to market any product or service. If required by law, we may disclose your NPI to appropriate government or law enforcement authorities. In such event, we will notify you of such disclosure if we may legally do so. 

### SAFEGUARDING INFORMATION

Our commitment to preserving the security and confidentiality of NPI applies to our former, current, and future customers. This commitment extends to any contact that is supplied by you on a Road ID, in an Emergency Response Profile or via the Road ID App. We never market to, or connect with, any contact you supply unless explicitly instructed to do so by you. 

### PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS

Road ID may, from time to time, send e-mail messages to you containing promotions for Road ID products. We will NEVER release your email to any third party or send you any communications on behalf of any third party. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, simply click the unsubscribe link that is contained in each email. 

### WHAT DOES ROAD ID DO TO PROTECT MY DATA

Road ID uses industry standard, 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to securely transmit personal information such as your name, address and credit card number. We utilize numerous online security, encryption, hashing and site verification services and techniques to ensure the security of our websites and databases. We store certain data in a highly-secured encrypted format. An industry-leading service regularly scans our sites for vulnerabilities. Our sites are also registered with identification authorities so that your browser can confirm Road ID’s identity before you transmit any personal information. Disclaimer: We take the security of your data very seriously and are fully committed to protecting your personal information. Please be aware, however, that no security measures can guarantee perfect security. 

We reserve the right to modify this policy, and will provide you with a new policy statement if we make material changes to our privacy or security practices. 

### QUESTIONS?

We’re easy to get in touch with and would love to chat via phone, email or live chat. Please check our “contact us” page on RoadID.com, MyRoadID.com or in the Road ID App for the most current contact information.
